[
  {
    "id": 0,
    "config": {
      "front": "XRXRRXRRR",
      "top": "XXXGXXXXX",
      "right": "XXXXGGGGG"
    },
    "solutions": [
      "U R U' R' U' y L' U L",
      "U R U' R' U' F' U F",
      "U R U R' U' F' U' F"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "config": {
      "front": "XXXRRXRRR",
      "top": "XXXXXXXRX",
      "right": "XGXXGGGGG"
    },
    "solutions": [
      "y U' L' U L U y' R U' R'",
      "U' F' U F U R U' R'",
      "R' F' R U R U' R' F",
      "U' R' F R F' R U R'"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "config": {
      "front": "XXWRRXRRX",
      "top": "XXXXXXRRX",
      "right": "GGXXGGXGG"
    },
    "solutions": [
      "U R U' R'",
      "R' F R F'"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "config": {
      "front": "XRRRRXRRX",
      "top": "XXXGXXGXX",
      "right": "WXXXGGXGG"
    },
    "solutions": [
      "y U' L' U L",
      "F R' F' R"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "config": {
      "front": "XXRRRXRRX",
      "top": "XXXXXRGXX",
      "right": "WXXXGGXGG"
    },
    "solutions": [
      "R U R'",
      "y2 L U L'",
      "y F U F'"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "config": {
      "front": "XXWRRXRRX",
      "top": "XGXXXXRXX",
      "right": "GXXXGGXGG"
    },
    "solutions": [
      "y L' U' L",
      "F' U' F",
      "y' R' U' R"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "config": {
      "front": "XXWRRXRRX",
      "top": "XRXXXXRXX",
      "right": "GXXXGGXGG"
    },
    "solutions": [
      "U' R U2 R' U2 R U' R'",
      "U' R U2 R' U' R U2 R'",
      "U' R U2 R' U R' F R F'"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "config": {
      "front": "XXRRRXRRX",
      "top": "XGXXXXGXX",
      "right": "WXXXGGXGG"
    },
    "solutions": [
      "Dw R' U' R U2 R' U R",
      "y U L' U' L U2 L' U L",
      "U' Rw U' R' U R U Rw'"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "config": {
      "front": "XXWRRXRRX",
      "top": "XXXXXRRXX",
      "right": "GXXXGGXGG"
    },
    "solutions": [
      "U' R U R' U2 R U' R'",
      "U' R U R' U' R U2 R'",
      "U' R U R' U R' F R F'"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "config": {
      "front": "XXRRRXRRX",
      "top": "XXXXXGGXX",
      "right": "WXXXGGXGG"
    },
    "solutions": [
      "Dw R' U2 R U2 R' U R",
      "Rw' U2 R2 U R2â€™ U Rw",
      "y U L' U2 L U2 L' U L"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "config": {
      "front": "XXWRRXRRX",
      "top": "XXXXXGRXX",
      "right": "GXXXGGXGG"
    },
    "solutions": [
      "U' R U' R' U F' U' F",
      "U' R U' R' Dw R' U' R",
      "F R U R' U' F' R U' R'"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "config": {
      "front": "XXRRRXRRX",
      "top": "XRXXXXGXX",
      "right": "WXXXGGXGG"
    },
    "solutions": [
      "U' R U R' U R U R'",
      "U y' R' U R U' y R U R'",
      "U2 R U' R' U' R U R'"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "config": {
      "front": "XRWRRXRRX",
      "top": "XXXGXXRXX",
      "right": "GXXXGGXGG"
    },
    "solutions": [
      "y' U R' U R U' R' U' R",
      "Dw R' U R U' R' U' R",
      "M' U' R U R' U' R U2 Rw'"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "config": {
      "front": "XGRRRXRRX",
      "top": "XXXRXXGXX",
      "right": "WXXXGGXGG"
    },
    "solutions": [
      "R U' R' U R U' R' U2 R U' R'",
      "R' U2 R2 U R2 U R",
      "U F' U2 F U' R U R'"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "config": {
      "front": "XXWRRXRRX",
      "top": "XXXXXXRGX",
      "right": "GRXXGGXGG"
    },
    "solutions": [
      "U' R U2 R' U F' U' F",
      "U' R U2 R' Dw R' U' R",
      "y' R U2 R2 U' R2 U' R'"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "config": {
      "front": "XXRRRXRRX",
      "top": "XXXXXXGRX",
      "right": "WGXXGGXGG"
    },
    "solutions": [
      "U' R U' R' U R U R'",
      "y L' U2 L U2 F U2 F' U F U' F'",
      "R U' R' U R U2 R' U2 R U' R'"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "config": {
      "front": "XGWRRXRRX",
      "top": "XXXRXXRXX",
      "right": "GXXXGGXGG"
    },
    "solutions": [
      "R U R' U2 R U' R' U R U' R'",
      "y L' U L U2 y' R U R'",
      "R U2 R' U R U R' U R U' R'"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "config": {
      "front": "XXRRRXRRX",
      "top": "XXXXXXGGX",
      "right": "WRXXGGXGG"
    },
    "solutions": [
      "R U' R' U2 F' U' F",
      "R U' R' U2 y L' U' L",
      "R U' R' U Dw R' U' R"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "config": {
      "front": "XXGRRXRRX",
      "top": "XXXXXXWRX",
      "right": "RGXXGGXGG"
    },
    "solutions": [
      "R U2 R' U' R U R'",
      "y L F' L' F L' U L U' L' U L",
      "U' R U' R' U2 R U2 R2 F R F'"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "config": {
      "front": "XRGRRXRRX",
      "top": "XXXGXXWXX",
      "right": "RXXXGGXGG"
    },
    "solutions": [
      "y' R' U2 R U R' U' R",
      "y L' U2 L U L' U' L",
      "R' F R F' R U' R' U R U' R'"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "config": {
      "front": "XXGRRXRRX",
      "top": "XXXXXRWXX",
      "right": "RXXXGGXGG"
    },
    "solutions": [
      "U R U2 R' U R U' R'",
      "U R U2 R2 F R F'",
      "R U' R' U R U' R' U R U R'"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "config": {
      "front": "XXGRRXRRX",
      "top": "XRXXXXWXX",
      "right": "RXXXGGXGG"
    },
    "solutions": [
      "U2 R U R' U R U' R'",
      "R U' R' U2 R U R'",
      "y F R U2 R' F'"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "config": {
      "front": "XXGRRXRRX",
      "top": "XGXXXXWXX",
      "right": "RXXXGGXGG"
    },
    "solutions": [
      "y' U' R' U2 R U' R' U R",
      "y U' L' U2 L U' L' U L",
      "U' R U' R2 F R F' R U' R'"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "config": {
      "front": "XXGRRXRRX",
      "top": "XXXXXGWXX",
      "right": "RXXXGGXGG"
    },
    "solutions": [
      "F' L' U2 L F",
      "y' U2 R' U' R U' R' U R",
      "Rw U' Rw' U2 Rw U Rw'"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "config": {
      "front": "XGGRRXRRX",
      "top": "XXXRXXWXX",
      "right": "RXXXGGXGG"
    },
    "solutions": [
      "R U R' U2 R U R' U' R U R'",
      "U R U' R' U' R U' R' U R U' R'",
      "U2 R2 U2 R' U' R U' R2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "config": {
      "front": "XXGRRXRRX",
      "top": "XXXXXXWGX",
      "right": "RRXXGGXGG"
    },
    "solutions": [
      "F U R U' R' F' R U' R'",
      "U' R U R2 F R F' R U' R'",
      "y U' L' U L U L' U L U' L' U L"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "config": {
      "front": "XRXRRXRRW",
      "top": "XXXGXXXXX",
      "right": "XXXXGGRGG"
    },
    "solutions": [
      "R' F R F' R' F R F'",
      "y L' U' L U L' U' L",
      "y' R' U' R U R' U' R"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "config": {
      "front": "XXXRRXRRW",
      "top": "XXXXXXXRX",
      "right": "XGXXGGRGG"
    },
    "solutions": [
      "R U' R' U R U' R'",
      "R U' R2 F R F'",
      "y L' U' L U2 F U' F'"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "config": {
      "front": "XRXRRXRRG",
      "top": "XXXGXXXXX",
      "right": "XXXXGGWGG"
    },
    "solutions": [
      "R U R' U' F R' F' R",
      "y L' U L U' L' U L",
      "y' R' U R U' R' U R"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "config": {
      "front": "XXXRRXRRG",
      "top": "XXXXXXXRX",
      "right": "XGXXGGWGG"
    },
    "solutions": [
      "R U R' U' R U R'",
      "F R' F' R F R' F' R",
      "y U' L' U' L U2 F U2 F' U F U' F'"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "config": {
      "front": "XXGRRGRRX",
      "top": "XXXXXXWXX",
      "right": "RXXRGGXGG"
    },
    "solutions": [
      "U' R' F R F' R U' R'",
      "R U' R' y L' U2 L",
      "l F' R U' R' U l'"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "config": {
      "front": "XXWRRGRRX",
      "top": "XXXXXXRXX",
      "right": "GXXRGGXGG"
    },
    "solutions": [
      "U' R U R' U F' U' F",
      "U2 R U R' F R' F' R",
      "U M' U R U' Rw' R U' R'"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 32,
    "config": {
      "front": "XXGRRRRRX",
      "top": "XXXXXXWXX",
      "right": "RXXGGGXGG"
    },
    "solutions": [
      "R U R' U' R U R' U' R U R'",
      "U R U' R' U R U' R' U R U' R'",
      "R2 U R2 U R2 U2 R2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 33,
    "config": {
      "front": "XXRRRGRRX",
      "top": "XXXXXXGXX",
      "right": "WXXRGGXGG"
    },
    "solutions": [
      "U2 R' F R F' U2 R U R'",
      "U F' U' F U' R U R'",
      "R2 u R U R' U' u' R' U R'"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 34,
    "config": {
      "front": "XXWRRRRRX",
      "top": "XXXXXXRXX",
      "right": "GXXGGGXGG"
    },
    "solutions": [
      "U' R U' R' U2 R U' R'",
      "U' R U' R' U R' F R F'",
      "R U R' U' R U' R' U R U' R'"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 35,
    "config": {
      "front": "XXRRRRRRX",
      "top": "XXXXXXGXX",
      "right": "WXXGGGXGG"
    },
    "solutions": [
      "U R U R' U2 R U R'",
      "U' R U2 R' U R U R'",
      "y U L' U L U2 L' U L"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 36,
    "config": {
      "front": "XXRRRRRRX",
      "top": "XXXXXXGXX",
      "right": "WXXGGGXGG"
    },
    "solutions": [
      "U R U R' U2 R U R'",
      "U' R U2 R' U R U R'",
      "y U L' U L U2 L' U L"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 37,
    "config": {
      "front": "XXXRRGRRG",
      "top": "XXXXXXXXX",
      "right": "XXXRGGWGG"
    },
    "solutions": [
      "R U R' U' R U' R' U2 y' R' U' R",
      "R U F R U R' U' F' R'",
      "R U' R' F' L' U2 L F"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 38,
    "config": {
      "front": "XXXRRGRRW",
      "top": "XXXXXXXXX",
      "right": "XXXRGGRGG"
    },
    "solutions": [
      "R U' R' F R U R' U' F' R U' R'",
      "Rw U' Rw' U2 Rw U Rw' R U R'",
      "R F U R U' R' F' U' R'"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 39,
    "config": {
      "front": "XXXRRRRRG",
      "top": "XXXXXXXXX",
      "right": "XXXGGGWGG"
    },
    "solutions": [
      "R U R' U2 R U' R' U R U R'",
      "R U' R' U R U2 R' U R U' R'",
      "R U2 R U R' U R U2 R2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 40,
    "config": {
      "front": "XXXRRRRRW",
      "top": "XXXXXXXXX",
      "right": "XXXGGGRGG"
    },
    "solutions": [
      "R U R' U' R U2 R' U' R U R'",
      "R U' R' U' R U R' U2 R U' R'",
      "R2 U2 R' U' R U' R' U2 R'"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 41,
    "config": {
      "front": "XXXRRRRRR",
      "top": "XXXXXXXXX",
      "right": "XXXGGGGGG"
    },
    "solutions": [""]
  }
]